I'm a reporter for the...
[Screams]
So, you want a story?
I'll give you the greatest story of destruction the world has ever known.
How is that for a story Miss Lane? Hahahaha!
Flash! True to his threat, the mad scientist, whose warnings have held the city in a grip of terror...
went on his rampage of destruciton at the stroke of midnight.
The deadly impact of his mysterious ray smashed the famous tower bridge,
hurling cars and pedestrians into the river below.
The police have warned everyone to remain in their homes.
This looks like a job for Superman.
It's Superman!
But, I thought the weapon? He isn't human!
[Jail door slams shut]
Congratulations Lois. That was a great scoop.
Yes chief. Thanks to Superman.