Up in the sky look!
It's a bird. It's a plane.
It's Superman!
In the endless reaches of the universe there once existed a planet known as Krypton.
A planet that burned like a green star in the distant heavens.
There, civilization was far advanced, and had brought forth a race of supermen.
Whose mental and physical powers were developed to the absolute peak of human perfection.
But, there came a day when giant quakes threatened to destroy Krypton forever.
One of the planet's leading scientists, sensing the approach of doom,
placed his infant son in a small rocket ship and sent it hurtling in the direction of the Earth.
Just as Krypton exploded!
The rocket ship sped through star-studded space,
Landing safely on Earth with its precious burden, Krypton's sole survivor.
A passing motorist found the uninjured child, and took it to an orphanage.
As the years went by and the child grew to maturity, he found himself possessed with amazing physical powers.
Faster than a speeding bullet.
More powerful than a locomotive.
Able to leap tall buildings in a single bound.
The infant of Krypton is now the Man of Steel!
Superman!
To best be in a position to use his amazing powers in a never ending battle for truth and justice,
Superman has assumed the disguise of Clark Kent,
Mild mannered reporter for a great metropolitan newspaper.
Kent, I want to see you.
Just received another threatening note.
Okay Mr White.
Lois, another note from the mad scientist.
Coming in chief.
Now listen to this warning. He plans to strike tonight.
Beware you fools. My Electrothanasia-ray strikes tonight at 12.
Total destruction will come to those who laughed at me and failed to heed my warnings.
Beware, I strike at midnight.
This nut may prove dangerous!
Kent, you help Lois follow up her lead. She may have an angle on this thing.
Yes sir.
But chief, I'd like the chance to crack the story on my own.
Well, I'll...
Thanks chief.
But, Lois?
Chief don't you think that's a dangerous mission?
The hour has come.